Montgomery Family Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Montgomery Family Papers, 1858-1974 (Box 4-33)
  - Miscellany, 1860-1974 (Box 23-33)
    - Marshall Hugh Montgomery (Box 27)
      - Automobile registrations, licenses, etc. (Box 27)
      - Awards, honors (Box 27)
      - Birth certificates, vaccination records, passports (Box 27)
      - Biographical data (Box 27)
      - Clippings (Box 27)
      - Historical societies (Box 27)
      - Invitations (Box 28)
      - Medical reports (Box 28)
      - Membership, identification, and credit cards (Box 28)
      - Memorabilia (Box 28)
      - Memorabilia, trips, (2 folders) (Box 28)
      - Middlebury College, Middlebury, Vt. (Box 28)
        - Alumni papers (Box 28)
        - Chi Psi fraternity (Box 28)
        - Souvenir programs and memorabilia (Box 28)
      - Printed material (Box 29)
      - Scholastic records (Box 29)
      - School papers (Box 29)
        - Grammar and high school (Box 29)
        - Middlebury College, Middlebury, Vt. (Box 29)
          - Freshman year (Box 29)
          - Sophomore year (Box 29)
          - Junior year (Box 29)
          - Senior year, (2 folders) (Box 30)
        - Souvenir dance programs (Box 30)
        - Wills and power of attorney (Box 30)
        - World War II (Box 30)
          - Clippings (Box 30)
          - Military record (Box 30)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 30)
    - Marshall Hugh and Giles N. Montgomery, drawings (Box 30)
    - Prudence I. Montgomery, (2 folders) (Box 31)
    - Roger E. Montgomery, scrapbook (photocopy) (Box 31)
    - William O. Montgomery (Box 31)
    - Beth Perkins Richardson (Box 31)
    - Robert K. Richardson (Box 31)
    - General (Box 31)
      - Christmas cards, (2 folders) (Box 31, Box 32)
      - Clippings, other family members (Box 32)
      - Correspondence with Library of Congress (Box 32)
      - Directory lists (Box 32)
      - Family genealogy (Box 32)
      - Greeting cards (Box 32)
      - Index to Montgomery family correspondence (Box 33)
      - Invitations, other family members (Box 33)
      - Registers accompanying Montgomery family papers (Box 33)
      - Printed material (Box 33)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 33)